stylishwife.com 2016-11-25

# Privacy Policy - Stylishwife

[Ekstrax.com](http://www.ekstrax.com/) uses features of latest web technology, to secure the data supplied by you, the visitor to our site.

The objective of this privacy policy is to educate you and keep you informed about the data collected by us when you come to the site.

The date collected from you is used for a specified particular purpose and this information will never be revealed to any third party

Numerous security precautions are put in place by the company to ensure the safety of this important data.

This privacy policy outlines the site’s purpose for collecting particulars from you and the modes used by us to capture these particulars.

The data and particulars given to us will be utilized keeping in mind the terms and conditions of the privacy policy.

By visiting this site and making use of this site you will be giving us you acceptance that you are in line with the privacy policy.

 **Cookies &amp; 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

 **What data do we gather?**

Particulars that are specific to the visitor is gathered by the site

These particulars given by the user, will be preserved in our records for future usage.

This may consist of important data needed for a specific objective

Sections of the user data usually retained my consist of details such as name, age, gender, email address, residential information and many others.

The given particulars of data with regard to a user is needed for many reasons

Thereby we utilize web technology of placing Cookies.

Cookies are needed for the objective of verifying the identity of the user and to follow the user’s browsing routine.

A cookie is placed in the user’s browser which is then transmitted back unchanged by the browser.

Cookies do not retain any user data and are there to improve the experience of the user.

When you express your opinions on a subject, other members have the right to comment on your views.

You may also utilize your social networking profile to comment on the posts and this will not be open to public viewing.

Apart from the details specified above, we may even collect a few other details information for technical purpose.

This data can help us in evaluating the popularity of our website.

This total collected information is not user-specific and is assembled with the singular purpose of improving the performance of our website.

This data is recorded in the form of a Log file.

A log file keeps tabs on all the information being transmitted from your browser.

 **How is the gathered data utilized?**

The gathered data will be utilized for a particular reason.

If you use the “[Contact Us](http://fashion.ekstrax.com/contact-us)” option, then you will be obligated to provide your contact details.

We will then touch base with you, by utilizing these particulars.

If you opt to sign up with us, then the particulars given by you are vital to validate your account.

We may dispense the personal information supplied by you with our third party affiliates, with the singular goal of your gain in mind.

You will be informed of such dispensing of information to third parties, beforehand.

If you want to offer your details, you can agree to the stipulation on that service.

 **  
****What if I give my details to a marketing affiliate of the site?**

When you click on the link of a marketing affiliate’s website; you will get redirected to our partner’s website.

The privacy policy specified here is applicable only to this website.

Thereby we are not accountable for securing the details given to the other websites.

Your data will be under the management of the affiliate’s website, with whom you are interacting.

Browse through the privacy policy provided on the website prior to offering personal data.

This policy is exclusively kept up for the EkstraX website and does not have any connection with any third party links given on the website.

 **Is the vital data given by me kept safely?**

We seek to employ the finest security devices as a means of preserving information supplied by our users safely.

Encryption mechanisms and many security barriers are put in place to preserve the safety of the data.

In spite of all arrangements, some reservations about the security mechanisms is natural.

The data may be vulnerable to attacks.

If you have any apprehensions regarding the reliability of the information supplied by you, then giving us feedback about this will be appreciated.

We will make sure that the finest security precaution are implemented to circumvent any harm to the important data.

We would like to emphasize that such occurrences have been very rare in the past and the details given over to us, are always protected with utmost diligence.

 **What if I get subscription letters/emails from the site seeking current details?**

Newsletters are sent from the official site, just keep members in the loop about the current happenings.

In case you get emails asking for important personal details, then you may regard it as a fraudulent gesture.

Keep us informed about such fraudulent activities.

Do not give out any data to such subscriptions from the affiliated/non-affiliated links.

 **What if I do not give out particular  data because I consider it confidential?**

When you utilize this site, the implication is you concede to the privacy policy.

In any case you may refrain from providing certain information if you consider it too confidential.

If you do not fill out all the mandatory fields you may not be able to take full advantage of all that the site provides.

 **Notice Regarding Online Behavioral Advertising**

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous data when you visit our Web site.

These companies may use non-personally identifiable data when you visit this and other Web sites to be able to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to appeal to you.

These companies normally use a cookie or third party web beacon to gather this data.

To find out details regarding behavioral advertising practice or to avoid of this form of advertising, you can visit www.networkadvertising.org.

 **Privacy Policy for Children**

We agree that young children are vulnerable to giving out private information easily.

The site has an age limit of 13 years and above.

People, who fall in this specified age group are allowed to give us the data.

 **Google DART Cookies**

Google as a third party vender uses a special DART cookie to serve ads on our website and other websites. If you don’t want to have this DART cookie on your computer, you can opt out .

 **Images on our website**

Many of the images used in our website are from different sources.

Because we employ many authors use of images from sites like Flickr, Google Images, Free Stock Photos etc.

We try and give credit of each image we use to the original source.

If you feel we are in breach of a copyright, please get in touch with us and we will try to find a solution for the problem in a way that is correct for all parties involved.

We do not say that we own the copyright to any image on this website unless ownership of said photo is explicitly stated.

If you copy, use or download any image from our website, we ask that you please credit the image to [Ekstrax.com](http://www.ekstrax.com/)

 **Right to make changes in the privacy policy**

The right to change the privacy policy is exclusively reserved by the website. If we make some alterations in the original privacy policy, we will keep you updated. If you persist with the site after the revised policy has been implemented, it implies that you agree with the new privacy policy.

And the rest of your post here
